Thank you, you can create a verdict for one presentation. Thank everyone for
coming here.
Thank you to the entire Councilor Corps who's right here. Also I want to say a
special welcome to our Council General Gassack from Boulder.
It's quite impressive. One of my father's most amazing accomplishments was when
he got together with Brad Hall, who was sitting over there, and Dave Kudhi, who
was sitting over there.
And they developed the initiative to have a nonstop weekly container service
directly between Cleveland and Boulder. It's an amazing feat we have now, and
it comes every two weeks of direct shipment from here to Althorpe. It's
fantastic.
Trading nations sell the bill to war. That was my father's favorite city. And
he lived that city. I remember growing up in many evenings, Arnie would call
and ask my mom, who sits right over there, to hang up.
It should mind if he brought an international client or two, or five, or eight,
over in about 30 minutes or so, that my mom was able to whip up an incredible
feast.
At moments and moments in time, we always had a wonderful evening while we used
our hands and feet to try to communicate with the fascinating people from all
over the world.
It was scary too. We grew up when there was a real iron curtain. A lot of you
probably remember that one. When he went there, he was gone for six weeks, and
you would not get any information or communication near that time.
And then suddenly he would bring it here again. And he had these wonderful
stories where he was jogging with the Russian army, or climbing the Great Wall
of China, and how he sold truckload plumbing supplies and traded them for a
part of the grain.
I mean, trading nations sell them to war, so for all of our cities, let's keep
trading. Thank you.